{
    "subject": "resource/Rimshot",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Technique",
    "human_readable": "Rimshot is a Technique.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9497513771057129,
            "question": "Is a rimshot considered a musical technique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8484167456626892,
            "question": "What is a rimshot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7154762744903564,
            "question": "In what context is a rimshot used?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6476683616638184,
            "question": "What instruments can produce a rimshot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6021116375923157,
            "question": "Who might use a rimshot in their performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5256101489067078,
            "question": "Can you describe the sound of a rimshot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5168903470039368,
            "question": "What kind of effect does a rimshot create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42587578296661377,
            "question": "How does a rimshot contribute to the overall feel of a piece of music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4248085916042328,
            "question": "Are there any variations or sub-types of rimshots?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28128013014793396,
            "question": "Can you think of any famous examples of rimshot usage in music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Rimshot is a Technique.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2201_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any variations or sub-types of rimshots?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2201_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How does a rimshot contribute to the overall feel of a piece of music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2201_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of effect does a rimshot create?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2201_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2201_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents discuss various aspects of rimshots as drumming techniques, including how they are played and their effects on sound. Therefore, the statement that \"Rimshot is a technique\" is supported by the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}